# Daniel Krydynski

Web Developer, UI/UX Developer, Interactive Media Designer

### (573) 803-9136 dkrydynski@gmail.com

### **PROJECTS**

### **Quicktools** — Internal technical tools platform

Implemented front end reactive framework using **Bootstrap 4** on a **Python Flask** web platform. Prototyped, designed, and developed the visual style using **Adobe Photoshop and XD** for the user experience and customized the **Bootstrap 4** framework to implement the new design into production.

### **KPI Tracker** — Internal report for student volunteer hours

Designed and developed a reporting tool using the **Grails** web application framework that utilizes the **Groovy** language to pull and display the data for how many hours the volunteers have completed and sorted the data into what projects the hours were associated with...

#### **EXPERIENCE**

### **Expedia,** Springfield MO— Technical Solutions and Tools Analysts

November 2019 - October 2020

Front end developer for internal tools created for the Quicktools platform that assists agents with troubleshooting and technical inquiries. Answered questions and performed troubleshooting for the Expedia and Hotels.com sites.

### **Anthem**, Indianapolis IN— Intern Developer

March 2018- October 2018

Gathered and updated documentation for programs alongside Business Systems' Technology team including developers and system architects for the conversion project to migrate their systems from IBM mainframes to Oracle databases.

### **Missouri State University,** West Plains MO— Junior Web Developer

June 2014 - May 2015

Designed and developed web applications for use by the school such as a Volunteer KPI tracker.

### **EDUCATION**

# Bachelor of Science, Technology Management with emphasis in Virtual Media

University of Central Missouri, Warrensburg MO - May 2019

# Associate of Applied Science, Computer Graphics and Programming with emphasis in Video Game Design

Missouri State University, West Plains MO - May 2015

#### **SKILLS**

UI/UX Design
Project Prototyping
Agile Methodologies
Web Design
Game Development
Adobe Creative Suite
Web Development
Project Management

### **LANGUAGES**

Html
CSS
Javascript
Python
C#
SQL
PHP
Groovy
Java
Swift

### **FRAMEWORKS**

Flask Bootstrap 4 Grails .net Gradle Unity Flash XNA Monogame